Who Is This Mission For?
You two, stay back, please!
That's a weapon I haven't seen very often.
Is it a mid-range type?
It would be difficult to run
away with both of them.
In that case...
He won't let me near him.
He's quite skilled at using his weapon.
What's going on?
A fight?
Wait... Is that guy swinging
something sharp around?
Th-This is not good.
Someone, go get security.
We're definitely bringing
attention to ourselves.
What should I do? This is going
to turn into a commotion!
Wow, this is amazing!
Huh? Miss Anya?!
Oh, no! If she sees me like this...
Wow! The lady from the circus is so cool!
Oh, it's just a street performance!
This really is a luxury cruise!
Sh-She really saved me!
It appears Miss Anya doesn't
recognize me, either.
Now's my chance.
Amazing!
This hallway has nothing I can use as cover.
There's a crowd watching us.
And behind me, the ones I want to protect.
That's making it difficult.
I can't get close to him at all!
No, that's not it.
My legs are heavy.
But why?
I'm hesitating to step forward?
I don't even have to worry about a
severe injury with a weapon like that.
You've got this, lady!
Hurry and beat that guy up
before Papa comes out!
I'll just have to risk getting hit,
grab his chain, and pull him down...
No, I think I need to make
this look more showy,
or they'll become suspicious.
What should I do? Um... Um...
You've got this, old guy!
Show us some better moves!
Tch. I messed up, and now there
are tons of people watching us.
What a pain.
Maybe I'll just mow her down
along with everyone else here.
Man, that was amazing!
I don't think I really
got the concept, though.
Mama is terrifying.
I think I'll start listening to
her a little more from now on.
There! Perfect! This should make her happy.
Ah! Papa!
I need to get back to the shop!
Where did you go, little girl?
There was a circus over there.
Anya was successful.
I was able to help Mama
and complete the mission
without Papa finding out.
Hero Anya cannot contain her excitement
from this epic adventure!
I'd like all of these items.
Y-You look lovely, sir.
This is perfect.
No matter how you look at it,
I am clearly a fun and happy dad.
Could you be any lamer? Yikes.
Let's go.
Man, just how crazy was the
domestic disturbance over there?
That ice pick was gross! Talk about scary!
Thank goodness there wasn't
a murder on this cruise.
I know, right?
Blue Lace No. 89 and
Mermaid eau de toilette...
These are different fragrances than
the ones I noticed at the mansion.
I guess she changed that along with her face.
There were at least two women and one man.
I guess the woman who had
no scent was the bodyguard.
It's me. Where are they headed?
I don't know.
There's a very high chance they've snuck
into the second- or third-class rooms,
Look at the time!
So you're over the bones?
but I haven't heard anything yet.
I guess I'll plant someone there.
Considering the ship's route,
they're probably going to try to defect
sometime tomorrow night or later.
When that time comes, they'll have
no choice but to show themselves.
Goodnight.
Keep up the good work.
Yeah.
What? No way!
By the way...
Did you find them?
No, not yet.
We've been ordered to go
to the third deck for now.
Man, talk about a useless informant.
He'd better not be thinking he'll
just take the money and run.
We're not gonna let that happen.
In fact, we can probably get back
what we paid him before
he disembarks the ship.
What are you gonna do once we get paid?
Let's see... First, I'm
gonna get some chicks...
I guess stupid people really
are just everywhere.
I guess I'll at least get prepared.
Ended up not buying anything
Hey, where are you going?
Our room's this way.
Mama's in trouble...
Yor is?
I mean, I'm sure she's working late,
but that doesn't concern you.
It's past your bedtime. Let's head back.
But Anya's adventure has only just begun.
She never contacted us,
so she's probably busy.
No one followed us, and no wiretaps.
Looks like we'll be able
to relax for a while.
It looks like the director has
prepared some food for us, as well.
We should be able to hole up in
here until the other boat arrives.
There, there. Quiet, now.
Man, that was scary!
What the hell is the deal with those guys?!
What's wrong with assassins?!
They just go around the ship shooting
guns and swinging sickles around!
You can't be serious! I wanna go home!
Stop making such a fuss, you moron.
But did you see how built those guys were?!
They're not human!
Honestly... You really are just a coward.
It's so pathetic I could almost cry.
Not you too, Young Master.
Make sure you don't grow
up to be like him, okay?
By the way, why'd you come with me?
You had no reason to put
yourself in all this danger.
You could've just stayed
in the new organization.
W-Well... that's because you're... I, uh...
What?
Er, I mean...
P-Please don't underestimate me.
I'm not so rotten that I'd forget
everything the boss did for me.
Right after the war,
when there was nothing to eat...
If it hadn't been for the black
market that the family ran,
I would've starved to death.
Here, you can have this.
Shh. Don't tell anyone else about this.
Hey, Olka. Where'd you go?
To this day, I remember exactly
how that bread tasted.
That's all the reason I need to stay here.
Zeb...
A-And did you know that
Hapoon's being all buddy-buddy
with pro-war extremists to get
rich through arms dealing?
He's a total piece of shit!
Leave this to me!
Even if Hapoon's lackeys come
after us, I'll beat 'em all to a pulp.
I'm sorry! That was a lie!
Good work, sir.
Earlier, you forgot about our secret knock
and went close to the door, didn't you?
I'm sorry. I'll be more careful.
I'd like the three of you
to rest up for tomorrow.
I'll leave Forger on guard at the door.
Wh-Who the hell can sleep in this situation?
What will you do, sir?
I'm going to have a look around this floor...
and if possible, thin out the threats.
You guys really are a piece of work.
People are trying to kill you,
and you're so calm.
You're not right in the head.
This is our mission.
So killing and getting killed
is just a given for you guys?
It's been over ten years
since the war ended.
But I guess war is always
just lurking around the corner.
As long as we people continue to
be people, conflict will never end.
Whether it's wartime or peacetime...
We are nothing more than
soldiers for our countries.
If necessary, I will signal with my footsteps.
Keep your guard up.
Oh, right. Understood.
Forger...
Y-Yes?
Concentrate on the mission,
or we're all going to die.
Man, he's scary! So that's what a pro is like...
The director is right. It's best
that the three of you rest.
Even if you just lie down for a bit.
You need to save your energy for tomorrow.
Please keep your shoes on so we
can move immediately if need be.
G-Got it...
I'm turning off the lights.
Come to think of it... I never was
able to contact Loid or Miss Anya.
But this isn't the time for that.
The heaviness I felt in my legs...
might've just been me being
scared that I would get hurt.
If those two ever see me so badly hurt
that I can't talk my way out of it,
I won't be able to stay in my home anymore.
That family's just for camouflage, right?
That's right, Yor.
I need to get my priorities straight.
Little
Brother
What am I...
What am I doing this for?
About 20 hours
until rendezvous
So tired... Why am I up so early in the
morning taking the doggo for a walk?
Borf! Borf!
Enough of your borfing, damn it!
I ain't a petsitter, nor a kiddositter, either!
I'm busy at work in the shadows!
Give me back my precious time, damn it!
Oh, what a cute doggie!
Huh?
Good morning.
I haven't seen you before.
Do you live around here?
Huh? Uh, yeah...
I hope I see you again sometime.
You wanna come live with me?
My name is Twilight.
I am the best spy in Westalis.
No matter the situation,
even in the face of death,
I've been trained to always keep my cool.
My observation skills, decision-making skills,
ability to respond to any situation...
Each of those has been honed to its peak.
That's how I made my way
in the world until today.
But...
Don't come over here!
Could you be any lamer?
I'd gotten ahead of myself.
There are still many unknown
things in this world.
I can't become overconfident based on
mere information and experience.
The root of everyone's fear is the unknown.
Death, the evil spirits we
cannot see with our own eyes,
neighbors and nearby countries...
Not knowing who or what they
are is what brings fear.
Some just accept the fact that
these things are incomprehensible.
In other words, they act
like they don't see them.
Others think they know and can label
everything, putting their hearts at ease.
I'm... I'm a secret agent.
I do not fear the unknown.
No... I fear it as I should,
and then deal with it.
Just as scientists shone
light into the darkness...
Just as they discovered
viruses and vaccines...
On the second day of this cruise,
I will somehow traverse the
difficult obstacle before me.
What?
We're done entertaining our guests?
It appears the mister and missus
got into an awful fight last night.
The missus was quite displeased when she
found Mister Grey had pooped his pants,
so she's not in the mood for fun.
I... I see.
So about the tourist attraction...
It's probably back to square one.
Don't worry about it. You two
didn't do anything wrong.
I will take care of the family.
You two are free to do
whatever you'd like today.
Y-Yes, sir.
Hell yeah!
Adventure! Exploring!
Hero Anya's adventures continue another day!
My observation skills, decision-making
skills, my ability to respond to any situation...
Super-exciting adventures!
Super-exciting detective hero...
I fell asleep yesterday, but I need to hurry
up and find Mama so I can help her out.
But...
Papa! Mama's in trouble!
We gotta hurry up and save her!
What?! What are you talking about?!
Impossible! Yor goes around having battles?!
I can't believe this! Oh my God!
That's bound to happen, so I can't tell him.
I have to figure out somewhere to lose Papa.
Papa, look! They have golfing!
Did you want to play?
I don't know why, but adults love golf.
My plan is to sneak away while
Papa is concentrating on golf.
H-He got a hole-in-one on every hole!
Bravo!
Shock! He's already done!
Go on. Now you try.
It's fun.
Grr! Hngh!
Calm down. Aim better.
It's about time for lunch.
Anya's gonna keep playing until it goes in!
Hmm... Having her experience
success is important.
I guess I'll let her keep
playing until she gets it in.
Decision. Response.
Stop yelling. You'll bother the other guests.
Grr!
I fell for Papa's trap and
ended up wasting time!
I need to think up the next plan.
Chew your food well.
Papa loves this thing called knowledge.
I'm sure I can keep Papa busy in here.
I've read all these books before.
Well, as long as she's having fun...
Oh! Shoot!
Puzzles are so much fun!
This looks like it'll be really hard if
I don't have Papa help me, though.
If I just need to line up the pieces,
I can finish in two minutes.
Let's see...
Observe.
I wasn't able to escape Papa,
and now it's time for dinner!
Heck, at some point, I forgot about Mama
and was just enjoying myself!
Mrgggh!
Why?!
Why are you glaring at me?!
You were clearly having fun!
Why do you look so grumpy now?!
Did I make a mistake somewhere?!
Calm down, Twilight. Face the unknown!
Does she hate me? Or is she just
going through a rebellious phase?!
At this rate, the Forgers
are going to fall apart.
D-Do you have a stomachache?
Are you all right?
Anya's worrying Papa?
I'm fine.
Anya is enjoying her adventure.
I see. Well, that's good.
But Mama's gone, so I miss her a bit.
Anya wants to be with Papa and Mama.
That's why I have to go help Mama by myself.
I see.
Yeah...
It would've been nice if Yor
could've had some time off.
She's still a very small child.
She may not be, but why don't we
just ask her if she's free tomorrow?
Do you know where Mama is?
No... But I'll leave a message
with the concierge.
Once we get a reply,
let's meet up with her.
All right!
I know. There are going to be
fireworks up on the deck later.
It's the main event for tonight,
so maybe Yor and the people she's
with will go and watch, too.
There'll be a big crowd, so I don't know
if we'll find her, but do you want to go?
Fireworks! I wanna go!
Yes.
Yes...
That was the director.
He's received word from the rendezvous ship.
They said they are ready.
We'll be meeting with them in four hours,
but we need to get ready.
And most importantly,
the enemy's closing in on this deck.
So we're going to leave this room
and go to another point.
Everyone, please change. We also have wigs.
A-All right.
It's me. Any movement?
I've intercepted an anonymous secret message.
It's different from the State
Security Service's frequency.
It could be a signal to the target.
Could be.
All right. Sending this to everyone...
Stand by at stage three positions
and ambush them.
All right. No enemies in the area.
Let's go.
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
The Symphony Upon the Ship